https://moultonlaw.com/privacy-policy/

.. Loading ..
Call Us:
(509) 328-2150
Our Address:
1220 N. Mullan Rd. Spokane, WA 99206
Find us on Social Media:
HomePrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
Can YOU share this for us?FacebookTwitter
Leave this field empty if you're human:
Contact Us Today! Moulton Law Offices P.S.
(509) 328-2150
Estate Planning, Financial Planning, Asset Protection, Probate and Estate Administration, Medicaid & more.
Moulton Law Offices
Get Directions to Moulton LawHave a moment to Review us on Yelp?
Check out Moulton Law Offices on Yelp
Latest TweetsEstate Planning Attorneys in Spokane, WA https://t.co/s59nVnr48A1 day agoHow to Utilize Life Insurance to Pay Long-Term Care Costs https://t.co/juyDPZYNd52 weeks agoWhat Happens to a Joint Account When my Spouse Passes Away? (Part Two) https://t.co/aKSXcBTYY63 weeks ago
About Us
Matthew M. Luedke
D. Michael Gunning
Melissa Murdock
Meet Our Staff
Client Care Program
Helpful Tips & Advice
Frequently Asked Questions
© 2021 Moulton Law Offices. All Rights Reserved.
Please Briefly Describe Your Situation:
Permission to contact you via email?
Please prove you are human by selecting the
Plane.
